Recently, Amanda Sills was caught online
going at her supporters because they
were asking about their orders and, you
know, I guess when the orders will be
shipped and all of these things. So, she
caught an attitude.
>> What's the hold up?
Please let me know where my order is.
You don't even got to worry
cuz now you don't got an order to worry
about. That's it.
>> I said this before, but every time she
steps out or she comes out, she's
frowned up. She looks mad. Um, she she
has an attitude that's very I don't
know, it's just very it's a turnoff.
Like when she when you see her, you
know, she just seems bitter to me. I
don't know why it is, but that's just
how she sees. And someone said, "Sounds
like a valid question." And that's why
your ass would get refunded, too.
Because if you think saying to someone,
"What's the hold up?" is a valid way to
approach them, then you were not raised
correctly. [music] And so when she does
this, it just further complicates how I
view her and how others view her because
she's always seems to has a pro to have
a problem with [music] something. And I
don't know, maybe maybe maybe I'll give
her the benefit of doubt of the doubt.
Uh because I don't know her personally
and I don't see her on a day-to-day
basis, but every time I happen to see
her, it's something negative or her
attitude and the way she talks is such,
you know, it's like a turnoff. I don't
know. I
I cannot be the only one that's sick and
tired of Amanda SS. Like Amanda SS ising
insufferable.
Why do she have to center herself in
everything every time?
>> But let me ask you a question. If you
ladies were a man, would you date and
get in a relationship with Amanda Seals?
The answer most likely is no. This video
isn't talking to Amanda because in my
opinion, she's a lost cause. If you
heard what she said in her rant, women
are alienating her, not just men.
>> What the is wrong with y'all? Never met
in my life. From free publications that
are supposed to be about uplifting black
people, WHICH IS ALL I HAVE DEDICATED MY
LIFE TO DOING. PEOPLE LITERALLY CANNOT
STAND THAT SOMEONE HAS STUDIED. THEIR
PASSION IS SO EXEMPLARY AND IS EXUDING.
>> NOW, no Amanda's rant [music] has
nothing to do with a romantic
relationship. Bible says it's better to
live on a corner of a rooftop
>> rooftop.
>> Than in the same room with a brawling
woman.
>> THAT'S BIBLE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> THAT'S WHAT THE BIBLE SAYS.
>> THIS WORD FEMINISM,
is that the word?
>> Mhm.
>> Feminism is a cap.
Feminism. That's a cap. That's the word
to sound cool to use.
>> Yeah.
>> Feminism is a cap. Craig, listen to
this, man. Cuz your opinion on this and
Darlene's opinion on this is very
important.
Most women who claim
feminism
are women who are not happy
>> with themselves. Mhm.
>> They can't say, "I'm not happy cuz it
sound like the truth."
>> Mhm.
>> So, they run to a word like feminism
so that they can have something to stand
on. But this is the truth. I'm going to
say this. There are so and and we gonna
talk about the guys too, but there are
so many women in America
who have
given guys
their body, but don't nobody want to be
a legacy with them. And she's starting
to realize that not only do men not like
a loud, contankerous, masculine,
intolerable woman, women don't like it
either. Because the way people like
Amanda Seals make money is through brand
deals. And if she can't get along with
the common person, what brand is going
to take a chance on her? Well, you
polite savages. Amanda Seals must be the
smartest dumbass in the history of the
world. How are you going to talk to your
customers like that? They're literally
sitting there trying to understand why
and where is the order that they paid
you for, but since you don't like the
way they asked, you wanted to go on and
cancel them. Well, ma'am, let's break it
on down here. This is not a situation
you are actually selling something. And
I understand that a customer is not
always right. But if the customer is not
always right, and you are wrong, both of
you are wrong. So, why don't you just uh
answer the question and go on because
they actually paid for something. You
see, when money is exchanged, somebody
has a right to be a little impatient,
especially if your shipping is not
taking the proper time that you said it
was going to take. But you don't want to
hear that because you always want to be
right. And it's one of those situations.
That's why it's known that you career
single feminist always have something to
say to somebody. Always need to be
right, but when it comes down to it,
you're damn wrong. You dig?
>> What's the hold up? Who are you talking
to? So when you guys are communicating
with small businesses this this this um
this holiday season, just remember that
nine times out of 10 you're talking to
the person who's actually uh doing the
job.
>> So that means that the service should be
absolutely exemplary. Well, this is the
problem especially in the community. I
see this a whole lot. You expect us to
just flee to you, spend our money with
you because you are you and not give us
the service that we deserve and that we
expect. You're not competitive in the
market because there's no place in the
market, no small business in the market
that's competitive that if you called
inquiring about shipping that they would
just go off, go ham on somebody. No
ma'am, what you are is the weakest link
and a reason why businesses fail. But
what we will all see apply savages is
that this is a prevailing issue in this
lady's life. And believe you me, it's
always someone else's fault. You dig?
>> This one kind of burns me, but I have to
say it.
Amanda Seals,
she is insightful and talented.
Yes, nuance is her ethos, but lately it
seems like she's been missing the
subtlety herself. Her points are big,
but the delivery feels untethered,
oversimplified, and even performative.
Not every disagreement is an existential
betrayal. He sometimes demands perfect
purity when the world is messy. Yeah. It
ends with da da da da da. And I asked,
"Oh, well, did they mention da da da da
da?" And she said, "Why don't you just
read it yourself?"
And that was the last day. And I just
SAID, "YOU KNOW WHAT? I DON'T GOT TO
TAKE THIS no more. I don't know who the
you talking to. I don't know why you're
even addressing me this way. We're in a
whole group of people together. We're
all discussing this. I'm actually
showing interest. And so that was the
last DAY AND I HAVE NEVER spoken to her
again. Just always in victim mode. Like
I I really feel like she's just one of
those Hollywood kids. And I just feel
like she's just feels like she's
entitled. You know, people have to do
this for me. They have to back ME UP. I
JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND LIKE WHY YOU out
here pulling a Mon'nique on is like it's
Ray HAS TO GO THROUGH DIFFERENT barriers
that you've gone through because you
simply have been grandfathered in. Why
you why are you out here talking about
what somebody DID TO ME? WHY THEY WON'T
LET ME IN ROOMS? I'm going to be honest
with you. I've spoken to several
highprofile figures that are in
Hollywood that are doing the invites.
She gets invited to all of them. And you
know what she does? And this listen,
this is according to them and according
to Amanda because she said that she was
on the spectrum, high functioning
spectrum. Okay? Now they say every time
she gets the invite, she goes in the
corner and don't talk to nobody.
>> They stop in.
>> So when it comes to you, it will behoove
you to look at Amanda Seals and do
everything in the opposite manner of
what she's doing and how she's acting.
Cuz virtually every man on this internet
has said to you indirectly that we do
not tolerate intolerable masculine
women. And if you stay this way, not
only will men ignore you, women at some
point are going to alienate you also.
Women should be FBI, feminine,
beautiful, and inspirational. Now, maybe
you work for somebody else and you
cannot control who you interact with at
work, but in your personal life, oh yes,
you can. You most definitely can decide
to not have any women, anybody in your
life that does not treat you with
respect. You can make those decisions.
And the thing is when you carry yourself
a certain way, when you treat yourself a
certain way, you will actually give
yourself permission to demand the best
from others. That's the key. You got to
carry yourself that way. Give yourself
permission to demand that people treat
you with respect. Address you with
respect. Let nothing slide. Uh-uh. When
someone wants to insult you, call it
out. Call her out on the mat. Nope. Your
name is so and so. Your name is Daryl.
Don't let them call you D. Say, "My name
is Darren. My name is Daryl." Do not
address me informally. Just think about
it. There's women out here who will lay
down with this dude,
lay down with that dude. And you know,
we men, we'll see him as long as we can.
>> But nobody want to build legacy with
them. Nobody want to build a legacy with
them. So I call them the tolerated
women.
>> That's a good one.
>> They're tolerated.
Everything they do in our presence, we
tolerate it to get what we want, then we
get away from them. And that don't make
us no better, fellas. But
the main goal that I'm trying to get to
in this conversation is we can't help
the women who don't get chose in
results. I mean, as a result, they get
upset with themselves in the world and
they come up with words like feminism
instead of telling, "You know what? I I
sleep with these guys. Don't nobody want
me." [laughter]
>> Polite savages. You better wake up. The
world you live in is just a sugarcoated
topping. There is another world beneath
it, the real world. And if you want to
survive it, you better learn to pull the
trigger.
>> Michael Jackson had to hit Man in the
Mirror. And it was designed to have you
think clearer, to have you understand
that change begins with yourself. But a
lot of folks out here, they just won't
change. Amanda Seal, she's one of them.
She'll be combative, but blame everybody
else and then wonder why she's failure
after failure. failing up, failing down,
failing left, failing right. Believe it
to her, she has nothing to change. You
see, a lot of folks think they're
infallible, but this infallibility is
only in their brain. And everybody knows
that Amanda Sales is absolutely
insufferable. You don't want to be
around her, untouchable. And she'll sit
here and tell you that it's somebody
else's fault. But it's time for us to
understand one real thing. She is the
absolute problem and the destroyer of
what she sees. So, as always, we're only
here to tell the truth, the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth as we see it.
And sometimes the truth is a bitter
bitter pill, but you got to keep it
real.
>> Some mothers are always trying to ice
skate up.
>> So, there's nothing left to do but get
up to it. Are you ready? Well, let's go.
>> She said, "Did you just hear it say she
was aut I said I did. I don't think
she's autistic. She probably took a test
online."
That's exactly what I said. I'm
artistic.
American Disabilities Association.
Please, please, I'm suing you. I can
sue.
Let's talk about this dodging of
accountability. Every [music] time a
modern woman is faced with something,
faced with bad behavior that she has to
look herself in the mirror, the first
thing that she's going to try to claim
is some trauma, something happened in
the past, autism, whatever she wants to
claim. It's absolutely cap. Cap among
cap. Ma'am, [music] don't you understand
that there's a lot of folks out here
that are actually afflicted with this
condition and that you are sitting here
playing in their face, running games in
their face
because I got a disability
that she hasn't been tested for because
the test is too much money. It's
$10,000. So, she just read on WebMD that
she was autistic. But this is the smart
individual that y'all are following and
out here capping or you just want
an excuse to be you. Act like you want
to act and do [music] what you want to
do. But the bottom line is this, ma'am.
Nobody believes you, ma'am. You were
over here with Supreme Cap, ma'am. And
nothing's going to excuse the fact,
ma'am, that you didn't got in an
argument with everybody you've been
around, ma'am. From Erica Badu to Issa
Ray. Ladies who agree with you can't
agree with you. So, the bottom line is
that it must be you.
>> Erica got me fired from a job. What am I
saying? Erica got me fired from a job.
[laughter]
her man was a writer and we were talking
one evening about a myriad of things and
he was saying how, you know, her agents
had a difficult time understanding her
and I said, "Well, she crazy." And he
was like, "What was that supposed to
mean?" I'm like, "Well, she's crazy. I
mean, like, these agents don't
understand crazy. They don't understand
that like we're not your regular
dangular, so why would they understand
her?" And he, I guess, took that as like
me disrespecting her. Meanwhile, I'm I'm
thinking of it as I'M TALKING ABOUT
MYSELF.
>> YOU ARE REALLY DUMB. For real.
>> Dear Amanda Seals, there will never come
a day that they can make me like you
until you apologize with your full chest
to Samaria Rice, Tamir Rice's mother.
Now, me, I don't follow Amanda. I
haven't followed Amanda, and it's for
one reason and one reason only. A few
years ago, she went after Tamir Rice's
mom, Samaria Rice, and called her a
clout chaser. pretty much saying that
this woman, a mother of a slain child
who was unal alive by police, was being
a clout chaser because she was calling
out want to be activist.
>> The seals calls out Charlemagne the god.
You got Amanda Sills going in on
Charlmagne.
Called out Charlemagne for having no
backbone. She went on to say Charlemagne
the god is not an intellectual.
She said he ain't dumb. He done read
some books, but he's really not a
intellectual. Right. She went on to say
when he be having people on the
Breakfast Club, he don't be challenging
them cuz he really ain't smart like
that, I GUESS, AT ALL. RIGHT. THIS IS
THE SAME WOMAN that done LIED ON THE
BROTHER, lied on a doctor, a black man
who was a doctor, who is a doctor.
Amanda Seals tried to, you know, put out
some lies about him and she got called
out for that or whatever. But
>> that many there shouldn't be that many
women in the world who claiming
feminism. You should be claiming what's
happening. You are not getting chose.
And I'm saying like a lot of attractive
women get chose, which is a very [music]
dumb reason to choose a woman if you're
smart. Yeah.
>> I mean, if you want an attractive woman,
but if that attractive woman is of no
substance and she's [music]
showing herself to be evil and
everything like that, you can't do
nothing with her. Nobody cares what you
say. We have to come to the conclusion,
Miss Seals. One conclusion for the new
year that you, ma'am, are the weakest
link. That you, ma'am, are the problem.
That you, ma'am, are the typical
protottypical anticist of the BS that we
need to leave behind. If you can't get
up and get with somebody and can't get
along, then hell, go on and go about it
by yourself. Build that empire by
yourself, be by yourself. Nobody cares
anymore. But I'mma tell you one thing.
When all of your friends are gone and
you have nothing but enemies surrounding
you, then ma'am, you've made a wrong
move, a wrong choice, and it's all on
you. You dig?
>> Never stop talking about the same way
that I will never stop talking about
when that broad had me kicked out of the
Emmys party. What do you mean? What if
the order was already on the way? I SHIP
THE ORDERS. WHAT PART OF THAT DO you not
seem to understand? I say this over and
over and over to y'all. I ship the
orders.
>> That's what they should start a a a
league of the unchosen women of America
and find shelter and dildos for them.
>> I'm just saying we have to be honest
about what's going on. It ain't it
shouldn't be that many.
>> Don't nobody want me. I give my body, my
throat,
the extra room in my house. I I told my
son he got a shed room with his
daughter.
They never get chose, dog. So they come
out with words like feminism cuz it
sound cool. But it's really the unchosen
women of America.
>> Proverbs 21 and verse 9.
>> IT IS BETTER
>> to dwell in a corner.
>> It is better to dwell in the corner
>> of the housetop.
>> OF THE HOUSETOP
>> THAN with a brawling woman
>> than with a brawling woman.
>> In a wide house.
>> BIG HOME. THAT'S WHAT WIDE HOUSE MEANS.
>> WIDE HOUSE.
>> BIG HOME. AND YOU GOT A BRAWLING WOMAN.
THE MOMENT YOU COME in the kitchen,
FIGHT FROM THE KITCHEN, FIGHT in the
dining room, fight in the living room,
fight in the bedroom, fight in the
bathroom. You can't even SIT ON THE
TOILET LONG ENOUGH WITHOUT FIGHTING.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> CAN'T EAT EGGS. CAN'T EAT GRITS.
FIGHTING.
>> FIGHTING.
>> CAN'T HAVE A PHONE CONVERSATION.
FIGHTING.
>> A TEXT MESSAGE. FIGHTING AND CUSSING.
>> YEAH, IT IS BETTER.
>> YOU CAN'T HOLD CONFERENCES IN YOUR
OFFICE WITHOUT YOUR WIFE THINK SHE'S
SUPPOSED TO BE IN THERE, TOO. WATCH over
you like a kid. That's right.
>> Thank you for [music] watching the Tip
Network. Follow us on all social media
outlets and ask yourself one burning
question. Can you handle the tip? Boom.
We're out.
>> We found true happiness.